{"data":[{"question":"The film lasted three hours with ________ of 15 minutes between part one and part two.","a":"an interval","b":"a pause","c":"a stop","d":"an interruption","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Interval: the period of time between two events, activities etc.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm very busy at the moment so it may take a ________ time to answer your letters.","a":"little","b":"few","c":"small","d":"some","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little\/little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"He was wearing a heavy overcoat to ________ himself against the cold.","a":"conceal","b":"protect","c":"cover","d":"wrap","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Protect somebody against something: keep someone or something safe from harm, damage, or illness ...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"It took Michael a long time to find a pair of shoes that ________ him.","a":"liked","b":"fitted","c":"agreed","d":"matched","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Fit: if a piece of clothing fits you, it is the right size for your body.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"________ the traffic was bad, I arrived on time.","a":"Although","b":"In spite of","c":"Despite","d":"Even","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Although (conjunction) + clause: used to introduce a statement that makes your main statement seem surprising or unlikely.\u00a0\n\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"He was unwilling to explain the reason ________ his absence.","a":"for","b":"why","c":"of","d":"that","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Reason for sth.\u00a0\n- Reason why + clause.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"John Jameson is a famous ________ who stole five million pounds from a bank.","a":"crime","b":"criminal","c":"criminally","d":"criminality","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Noun phrase: (a\/an) adj + noun.\u00a0\n- Criminal: someone who is involved in illegal activities or has been proved guilty of a crime.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"________ your own business can cause a lot of financial worries.","a":"Manage","b":"Managing","c":"Manager","d":"Manageable","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Both gerund and infinitive can be subject: \n+ Gerund: are often used when actions are real, concrete or completed.\u00a0\n+ Infinitive: are often used when actions are unreal, abstract, or future.\u00a0\n- Manager: refers to person.\u00a0\n- Manageable + noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The surgeons tried their best to save his life, but unfortunately the operation was ________.","a":"unsuccessfully","b":"successful","c":"successfulness","d":"unsuccessful","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adverb modifies Verb.\u00a0\n- Adj modifies Noun.\u00a0\n- \"But unfortunately\"- implies negative meaning.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"I understand ________ what you are saying.","a":"perfect","b":"perfectly","c":"perfection","d":"imperfect","answer":"2","explain":"\n- An adverb goes after understand","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"}]}